[{"question": "Which of the following are true of a default VPC? (Select TWO.)", "answers": ["A default VPC spans multiple regions.", "AWS creates a default VPC in each region.", "AWS creates a default VPC in each Availability Zone.", "By default, each default VPC is available to one AWS account."]}, {"question": "Which of the following is a valid CIDR for a VPC or subnet?", "answers": ["10.0.0.0/28", "10.0.0.0/29", "10.0.0.0/8", "10.0.0.0/15"]}, {"question": "Which of the following are true regarding subnets? (Select TWO.)", "answers": ["A VPC must have at least two subnets.", "A subnet must have a CIDR that\u2019s a subset of the CIDR of the VPC in which it resides.", "A subnet spans one Availability Zone.", "A subnet spans multiple Availability Zones."]}, {"question": "What\u2019s the difference between a security group and a network access control list (NACL)?\u00a0(Select TWO.)", "answers": ["A network access control list operates at the instance level.", "A security group operates at the instance level.", "A security group operates at the subnet level.", "A network access control list operates at the subnet level."]}, {"question": "Which of the following is true of a new (custom) security group?", "answers": ["It contains an inbound rule denying access from public IP addresses.", "It contains an outbound rule denying access to public IP addresses.", "It contains an outbound rule allowing access to any IP address.", "It contains an inbound rule allowing access from any IP address.", "It contains an inbound rule denying access from any IP address."]}, {"question": "Which of the following is true of a VPC peering connection?", "answers": ["It\u2019s a private connection that connects more than three VPCs.", "It\u2019s a private connection between two VPCs.", "It\u2019s a public connection between two VPCs.", "It\u2019s a virtual private network (VPN) connection between two VPCs."]}, {"question": "What are two differences between a virtual private network (VPN) connection and a DirectConnect connection? (Select TWO.)", "answers": ["A Direct Connect connection offers predictable latency because it doesn\u2019t traverse theinternet.", "A VPN connection uses the internet for transport.", "A Direct Connect connection uses AES 128- or 256-bit encryption.", "A VPN connection requires proprietary hardware."]}, {"question": "You need to deliver content to users in the United States and Canada. Which of the following edge location options will be the most cost effective for your CloudFront distribution?", "answers": ["United States, Canada, and Europe", "United States, Canada, Europe, and Asia", "United States, Canada, Europe, Asia, and Africa", "All edge locations"]}, {"question": "What is a NACL?", "answers": ["A logically isolated section of AWS", "A table of rules that directs traffic flow in a network", "A firewall on the subnet level", "A firewall on the instance level"]}, {"question": "Which of the following will create subsections of a VPC?", "answers": ["ELB", "Subnet", "Security Group", "Internet Gateway", "NACL"]}, {"question": "VPCs span all of these except for\u00a0______.", "answers": ["Availability Zones", "AWS Regions", "AWS resources", "Subnets"]}, {"question": "Which of these statements is true of subnets?\u00a0(Select THREE.)", "answers": ["We can not add more than one subnets in each AZ.", "The default VPC already has subnets created for each AZ by default.", "Subnets can span AZs.", "Subnets cannot span AZs.", "We can add one or more subnets in each AZ."]}, {"question": "What does a route table do?", "answers": ["Connects resources within a VPC to the internet", "Allows or denies inbound/outbound traffic on the instance level", "Directs traffic within a network", "Allows or denies inbound/outbound traffic on the subnet level"]}, {"question": "In this scenario, we have a NACL with the following rules.Rules\u00a0 \u00a0TrafficRule#1 Allow SSHRule#2 Allow HTTPRule#3 Deny AllRule#4 Allow AllWhich is true based on the rules within this NACL?", "answers": ["All traffic will be allowed", "All traffic will be denied", "All traffic except SSH and HTTP will be denied", "SSH traffic will be denied"]}, {"question": "What is a VPC?", "answers": ["A logically isolated section of the AWS Cloud", "A subsection of a private network", "A type of AWS account", "A public cloud"]}, {"question": "How many VPCs are created by default in a region?", "answers": ["4", "2", "3", "1"]}, {"question": "Which of the following is descriptive of an Internet Gateway?", "answers": ["A logically isolated section of AWS", "A stateful firewall for inbound/outbound traffic", "A stateless firewall for inbound/outbound traffic", "A route to and from the internet"]}, {"question": "Which of the following will connect instances within a VPC to networks outside of the VPC and provides Internet access for the VPC?", "answers": ["Subnet", "Route Table", "Internet Gateway", "NACL"]}, {"question": "How many Internet Gateways can be attached to a VPC at a time?", "answers": ["Unlimited", "2", "1", "4"]}, {"question": "What does VPC stand for?", "answers": ["Virtualization Platform Cloud", "Virtual Private Cloud", "Virtualized Private Cloud", "Virtual Public Cloud"]}, {"question": "You have two EC2 instances hosting a web application. You want to distribute 20 percent of traffic to one instance and 80 percent to the other. Which of the following Route 53 routing policies should you use?", "answers": ["Weighted", "Multivalue Answer", "Simple", "Failover"]}, {"question": "Which AWS service will inspect web traffic to your applications and apply rules and security controls based on the contents of the traffic?", "answers": ["CloudWatch", "Shield", "WAF", "CloudTrail"]}, {"question": "Resources in a VPC need to be able to resolve internal IP addresses for other resources in the VPC. No one outside of the VPC should be able to resolve these addresses. Which of the following Route 53 resources can help you achieve this?", "answers": ["A public hosted zone", "Domain name registration", "Health checks", "A private hosted zone"]}, {"question": "Which of the following Route 53 routing policies doesn\u2019t use health checks?", "answers": ["Simple", "CloudWatch alarm", "Endpoint", "Calculated"]}, {"question": "From where does CloudFront retrieve content to store for caching?", "answers": ["Regions", "Origins", "Distributions", "Edge locations"]}]